I think I built the ultimate claw design
skill for websites and I'm going to give
it to you guys for completely free. This
thing helps you figure out what type of
website you're looking for, generates
you all the assets or takes the assets
you already have and then creates an
interactive scrolling style of website.
So, it's not just your generic AI slop.
You can see in this one we're literally
going through a journey because this is
like a travel agency that's trying to
get clients to book in with them. Here's
my original website that I had built
with Claude. It's it's okay, right? It's
nothing crazy. And what I did is I said,
"Hey, Claude, look at my website. use
this skill and transform it. And this is
what it created. It kept all the same
copy. It kept all the same branding and
the same feel, but it turned it into
something that's way more interactive
and it almost like hooks you in to make
you want to keep scrolling through the
rest of the website to actually see
what's to come. It has a way more
premium feel than the way that you
typically get your websites if you're
building with Claude. So, I call this
skill scroll craft because the whole
idea is that you're actually having this
hook in the viewer by making the scroll
correlate to something that's going on
on the actual page. So, on top of the
idea that Claude should always be
looking for opportunities to make the
scroll feel interactive, there's also
design elements in the skill as well.
Things like spacing, typography, feel,
taste, all that kind of stuff. And what
you'll notice about the skill is it's
not just one specific template, right?
Every single one of these websites that
I've shown you guys so far comes out a
little bit different. And that's why the
interview section of this skill is so
important because it asks you, what type
of website do you want? What do you want
the field to be? It really thinks about
the user journey when they would
actually open up the site and scroll
through. It's almost like short form
content. If you don't get hooked right
away, you're not as interested. You can
see some of these are super professional
and super editorial, like this one. This
is a very like trusted feel, but it
still has a bunch of scroll animations
and it feels more premium. It just gives
it so much more depth when there's
something else going on. Love this
little animation right here. And hopping
back over to the perk form example. I
had it generate two versions for me. So,
this is the first one. They both keep
the consistency in like the color scheme
and the vibe and the actual copy that's
trying to be communicated through. The
entire site doesn't have to be super
flashy and animated. This one was mainly
just kind of like that first hero
section. But here's another version of
it that's a little more simple at the
front because we're just zooming in a
little bit. And then we get into this
thing where it's like we're only
focusing on one thing at a time and the
user is scrolling through and the user
is in control of what they're actually
going to be looking at. And now we can
see the three different product shots,
the three different flavors and the call
to action at the end. Anyways, there's
so many different examples that I've
generated and you can see that they all
just have different vibes and different
styles, but they all are still unique,
right? like they're going to make the
client remember your business. So
anyways, let me quit yapping and let's
just talk about how the skill works, how
you get it, and let's do a live example
together. So real quick, if you want to
get the skill, it's completely free. Go
to my free school community link in the
description, go to the classroom, click
on all YouTube resources, and everything
that I give away for free ever is always
in here. So just hop in and grab the
skill. And so in this video, I'm going
to be using the Cloud Code desktop. I'm
also going to assume that you have a
little bit of Cloud Code knowledge. So
if you're just starting out at the
complete beginning, go ahead and watch
the 6-hour course I have or I guess
it'll be up here for non-coders. watch a
little bit of that course, get familiar
with Claude Code and then come back in
here and build some crazy websites. So
that skill will be a plugin that you can
install or you can actually just take
the actual folders and files and put it
into your cloud, whatever you want to
do. But now you can see if I come in
here and I type scroll, we have the
scrollcraft skill which says to build a
premium scroll driven interface landing
page for any business. So whatever type
of product you have or service, you can
do it in here. We saw a ton of different
examples. We saw physical products as
you could see. We saw a personal
branding website which was for myself,
another agency that was like travel. So
you can do a lot of different things
with this skill. So let's actually make
a real website for myself for AI
Automation Society. So right now this is
AI Automation Society's website. We've
got this nice little globe animation up
top, but then there's nothing really too
special. There's a few pictures. We
tried to make it look, you know, at
least sort of branded and trusted, but
there's nothing too engaging at all. I
mean, some of the cards move a little
bit, but let's try to like redo this
website. So, I'm looking to use this
skill to redo my AI Automation Society
website. I'm looking for this one to be
premium trusted. I'm looking for this
one to be more editorial rather than a
bunch of different AI generated assets
and not like a a world that we'd be
flying through. I'm looking for this one
to be more premium. I'm basically just
going to start off like that because the
first part of the skill is going through
sort of like an interview process to
really understand the type of vibe
you're looking for because like like
this one, right? This is a bunch of AI
generated assets that creates us like
this flying world effect where we have
like we're bouncing around. This one
also has AI generated assets, but it's a
bit more um like hypy. It's a bit more
energetic with, you know, a product that
we're trying to sell, a physical
product. So, I think the vibe that I'd
be looking at for this a Automation
Society one is maybe something a little
bit more like this that has like subtle
animations and subtle scroll. So, you
can see we're not starting from zero. It
has our site, it has our brand assets,
and it has other builds that we've done.
And now it's going to interview us. So
right now, let's say you have no
business at all. You don't know what
you're going to build a site for. Just
go ahead and do everything with AI
generated assets just to play around
with the skill to see how it works. And
the way that this skill specifically
does it is it uses key.ai. So if you've
never used key.AI, it's kind of like
open router but for like image and video
models. You can choose between all these
different ones. So if I actually go to
my logs real quick, you can see some of
my most recent generations were um
results that we just used. So this can
thing, we also have like the the phase,
we have the cup, we have all of these
assets that we've been generating for
these websites, videos or images. And
all you have to do is go into here, grab
an API key, and then put that in your
environment variables of the Cloud Code
project, and then it'll be able to just
hit this for all of the assets that it
needs, and it will fill in the gaps.
It'll automatically create images, and
then turn those images into videos, and
it will stitch the videos together.
It'll do whatever it needs to do because
the skill tells it how. But here we are.
We have some questions coming. So what's
the scroll journey? What does the
visitor hit first and in what order
after that? So, do we want to open with
the proof receipts first like these big
stats? Do we want to start with Nate's
story? Do we want to start with inside
look? I think we want to just start up
top with the receipts. That's what it
recommended. Then it asks, "What must
the visitor believe by the end? One
sentence, not a feature list." And so,
what I'm actually going to do is kind of
like put in a mission statement here.
So, I'm just going to paste in what we
say. Go ahead and hit next. What real
assets do you have? This decides how
much gets generated versus graded from
what you own. photos of us and events,
community screenshots, workflows, what
do we have and what does it need to go
generate? Just use the pictures that are
already in there. So like there's one
image of um me speaking. There is also
an image of like all of us at one of our
events. It's like it looks kind of like
a Zoom call, but those are the only two
images I gave you besides the one at the
bottom that says meet our founder and
the merch image. So those are the images
you should work with. But actually, it'd
be cool if you generated a few images of
like like if you generated images that
weren't necessarily photorealistic, but
they were sort of like looking at
educational environments. So maybe like
a nice style of I'm blanking on what the
style would be called. I guess maybe I'm
thinking this like low poly geometric. I
guess we'll try that. Like a
minimalistic geometric lowpoly human
figures. you know, if there were maybe
scenes that go along with the
certification or the events or AIS plus
like people having wins, people teaching
each other, people working together,
just keep it minimal and make it match
the color scheme and the brand
guidelines of AIS. But just something
else to give it a little bit of flavor
here that we can sync up with some
scrolls. Finally, it says one thing this
site should do that no sites you've seen
does. This becomes a signature move.
Every claim has a receipt. Nothing on
the page is asserted without a source.
Yeah, I guess we'll go with that one for
now and hit submit. So, that's where you
can get really, really specific. And the
better idea you have of like what you
want, feel free to put that in there.
But if you don't have an idea, that's
the beauty of this skill is it knows a
bunch of taste as far as like what makes
good scroll animations. As you saw all
those examples I showed you, there were
so many different things. Like here's
one I didn't love, but this one has at
the end like some really cool things
where it looks like um like flight
cards, right? It looks like these
departure cards and the destinations and
we see this syncing to the scroll. So
really what's important to me is that
everything on the site basically the
user is in control with their mouse
because they're basically controlling
what's happening and they can go
backwards, they can go forwards and
whether that be controlling like
scrolling images like that or actually
just having like numbers fade in or
appear like that or this image kind of
like fades out as well. It's really just
about that idea of the scroll sinking to
something. Few more questions here.
Where should this page feel calm and
where should it feel intense? I'm just
going to go through some of these other
design questions and then um I'll check
them into you guys when anything
interesting is happening. Lately, I've
been finding that you can really
instruct AI models a little bit more
emotionally than you used to in the
past. Like I'm telling this thing what I
want it to feel like and what I want the
motivation to be and it I really have it
thinking about if it was the user and
clicking through and scrolling through
what would it feel and how do we sort of
like manipulate that emotion as much as
we can. But anyways, this thing is
building now. I will check back in with
you guys when we have something to look
at. One thing I want to call out here,
after it started generating some of
these images and stuff with key.AI, it
started to build the website. And now
that it's building it, it does
verification. So it says now the part
the harness can't judge, zooming into
key frames. So it's literally taking
screenshots of the site and it's going
to investigate and inspect them to make
sure that nothing is off and nothing is
wrong. And so that's how hopefully it's
able to give us something on the first
shot that's a lot better than if it
didn't do this verification pass. So I
just wanted to call that out. That
should be going on in the background.
And that's why it's so important to
watch Claude as it's working. You get a
feel for how the harness actually
behaves. Okay, so here we are. This
thing has finished up. It took about 30
minutes, I believe. And we have right
here a screenshot that basically goes
through the flow. So it kind of went
through the scroll itself to see what
the vibe is like. So let's click in. I
haven't looked at this yet. Okay, so
right off the bat, it definitely feels
kind of like that professional almost
like a report sort of vibe. It's very
editorial in that way. It's very
professional. First glance though, it
looks pretty boring. So hopefully as we
start to scroll through we get some cool
stuff going on. We have live data. So it
actually went ahead and pulled live
numbers right now. This is like as of
today. This I believe also if I go to my
free school real quick um 441.5.
This is literally as of today. So it
pulled up literally fresh numbers. We've
got preparing as many people as possible
for a new way of working. AI is
reshipping how work is done. Oh,
interesting. Look at this. I just
noticed this. I'm going to refresh. It
says right now sourced zero out of nine.
So on the left hand side we have
sources. As I scroll down, we start to
unlock new sources. So, that's kind of
cool. Um, okay. So, now we have switched
into sort of like a dark mode. It says
it stopped being a room a long time ago,
and we're kind of growing the members
and we're growing the global presence,
which I really like. Although, I think
that this animation goes a little too
quick. Like on a typical scroll, that's
too fast. So, we can have it slow that
down, which I'll show you guys. We want
to slow this down, but that's very nice.
I like that graphic. We have exhibit A,
the room on an ordinary Tuesday. It's
the live call right here. We have some
testimonials right here. Glenn, Casper,
and Amy. Very, very cool. And all three
of those people are actually on this
call, too. Glenn, Casper, and Amy. I
love that. As we keep going down, we've
got four quarters on a public
leaderboard. Wait a minute. Okay, so it
literally went I don't know where I kept
these, but it went and found these
screenshots because this info is not on
the original site. We don't have these
screenshots anywhere. So, it had to go
find those somewhere. It found these
leaderboard pictures and put them in
here for our four out of four school
game wins in 2025. And then we have
right here, um, exhibit F, which was the
AS Plus classroom. Okay, so we have a
sort of like a horizontal scroll coming
along there. We've got six out of nine
sources. The founder, he was not a
developer when he started. Graduated
from the University of Iowa. Cool. It's
got this picture. Nice. Um, we will have
to fix this caption though cuz that was
not AIS Live. That was Africa AI. So,
there's a few things that we'll want to
fix and touch up. But here is a video
that we've got the sort of the geometric
low poly. This is for the certification.
So, it's like they're teaching. Very
cool. Um, I might need to fix some of
this copy. Where does this button link?
Okay, that links to our free school.
We'll have to change some of the stuff
up. um everything this page just
claimed. What is this? Oh, okay. So,
this kind of runs through those nine
sources. I don't know if I love that,
but I don't know. Kind of cool. We have
the free community right here, and then
we have AS+, which takes us to AS+.
Okay, very cool. So, I believe that we
have our merch there. We have the
certification once again. And then
that's basically the end. Cool. So, this
is obviously a very different vibe than
the original AIS website. It's a
different vibe, but it has similar feel.
You can tell it's still the same brand.
It's still the same um guidelines,
right? So, now it's just a matter of we
can get pretty nitpicky here. What are
the little little things that we don't
like and what are the little things that
we want to have changed about the site,
but overall, I think that this is a very
unique site. Haven't really seen many
websites like this. All right, so I've
got a little bit of feedback here about
the site. First of all, I want to say I
think you did a good job. You got
creative and you took in my feedback,
which was good. I like how you went and
pulled live numbers. That was really
nice. So, as far as the hero section,
it's a little bland when someone first
loads up the page. It's a little bit
bland and it doesn't feel I don't know,
it doesn't feel very premium. So, maybe
you can add a little bit of depth here
or maybe just some I don't know, do
something to this hero section because
that's like where we want to hook in the
audience. Now, I really like this first
part about the reach. I really like the
scroll animation with the the globe
filling up. I feel like that feels very
on brand. It shows the members growing,
although it scrolls too fast. So, if you
could slow this down significantly so
the users can actually scroll and
realize what's going on, that would be
great. Um, as we continue to go down
here, I like exhibit A. I like the room
about the community. I like the
testimonials here. I think that's good
for now. I think maybe if you could just
add some more. I don't know, like it
just feels a little bit bland. I like
how we get into exhibits B through F. I
like the sideways scroll, but it just
once again feels a little bit bland. And
I think that you can work in some
elements here to make this just feel
more premium. Um, there's nothing
special about the founder section. Maybe
we have something like a scroll
animation here as well, just to make it
less bland. Um, I like this little
animation for the certification, but it
feels like it doesn't quite last long
enough. Maybe you could slow it down or
make that a little more exaggerated.
Also, the link for the certification, if
you could grab the actual link that's
linked in the main site, on the main AIS
site, the certification link takes you
to like a waiting list, I believe. So,
the reserve your place. Yeah, it should
take you to a waiting list. So, grab
that link and make sure that that's on
the actual site here that you're
building for us. And honestly, I don't
love the register. Let's just get rid of
that section. I like the idea you had
with like making this scrolling and
adding more animations and making this
interactive, but I don't like the
register. So, you can get rid of that.
And yeah, I think the rest at the moment
is fine. Let's just kind of clean up
some of the stuff. Okay. So, I'm going
to shoot this off. We'll give this
feedback and I will check in with you
guys when we get the stuff back. Okay.
So, next version came back. We can see
that we have it open on our local host.
It says the register is gone. The globe
got slowed down a little bit. A new hero
section. So, now it's a magazine cover.
So, we'll see what that looks like. And
everything else that we wanted has been
changed. So, let us go back over here
and open up this link. And we see Okay,
nice. I like how that kind of came in.
If I go give it this refresh, you can
see how that scrolls in. I like that.
Um, we have a little picture of me over
here. And we have same copy, same feel,
nice little blue um highlight on the
mouse. That might be a little too much,
but anyways, this Okay, cool. This is
scrolling a lot slower now. So, we're
able to sort of watch the numbers go up.
We're see sort of able to watch the map
kind of get taken over by these blue
dots and all these connections. I really
like that animation. I think that's
really cool. We can see here the room on
an ordinary Tuesday. There's no
animation to this part. Maybe we should
have like this image kind of like reveal
or we should have the text come through
as if it was being typed or something.
We could easily add that fix. We go down
to this part. It added like these little
colors behind these. These cards are
kind of like dynamic. If we put the
mouse over it and we hover um this one
scrolls in nice. So that's kind of what
I want to do to um maybe up here. I want
to have it scroll in almost like a
typewriter. And then we have the
coursework is not a credential. Oh,
nice. So it actually changed all this
copy as well. It made this more specific
to the actual cohort. And then this
links to the right spot. Okay. Very
cool. So as you can see the register is
now gone as well. So all the changes
that we asked for have been completed.
So what I wanted to highlight here is
that I haven't yet created an example
that looked like this. And that's what I
think is so cool about this skill that I
built is that it utilizes design
principles, but it's not going to give
you a template. It's still going to very
much give you something that's unique to
the way that you describe, you know, the
emotions and the journey and the goals
of your business or whatever wherever
you're making the website for. And by
the way, I did have it regenerate real
quick with this coming in more like a
typewriter effect. So I think that's a
lot cleaner. You can see it did a really
cool animation here where it literally
makes each of their faces come in each
of the screens one at a time. So that's
super slick and I love that it you can
see it has a bit of a bug when you have
to reload like that, but otherwise comes
in pretty clean. I like that a lot. So
anyways guys, just remember if you want
to download the skill, go to my free
school community. It will be linked in
here with a post. It'll also be in the
classroom, all YouTube resources, AI
skills. You can find it many places in
here. But go check out the skill if you
want to build some sites like this. But
that is going to do it for today. Okay,
so if you guys enjoyed, you learned
something new, please give it a like. It
helps me out a ton. And as always, I
appreciate you guys making it to the end
of the video. I'll see you on the next
one.